http://www.nccn.org/about/privacy.aspx

| Contact Us
Follow us on:
Treatment of Cancer by Site
Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia (Adult and AYA)
Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia (Pediatric and AYA)
Gastric Cancer
Gastrointestinal Stromal Tumors (GIST)
Gestational Trophoblastic Neoplasia
Hairy Cell Leukemia
Head and Neck Cancer
Hepatobiliary Cancers
Hodgkin Lymphoma (Adult and AYA)
Hodgkin Lymphoma (Pediatric and AYA)
Myelodysplastic Syndromes
Myeloid/Lymphoid Neoplasms with Eosinophilia and Tyrosine Kinase Fusion Genes
Waldenströms Macroglobulinemia/Lymphoplasmacytic Lymphoma
NCCN Guidelines for Detection,
Colorectal Cancer Screening
Genetic/Familial High-Risk Assessment: Breast, Ovarian, and Pancreatic
Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia
Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia (Pediatric)
NCCN Guidelines with NCCN Evidence Blocks™
NCCN Framework for Resource Stratification of NCCN Guidelines
(NCCN Framework™)
International Review of NCCN Framework™
NCCN Harmonized Guidelines™
NCCN Imaging Appropriate Use Criteria (NCCN Imaging AUC™)
Subscribe to the NCCN Templates
Review the NCCN Chemotherapy Order Templates (NCCN Templates®) User Guide
Live Meetings
NCCN 2021 Virtual Congress™: Breast Cancer with Updates from the 2020 San Antonio Breast Cancer Symposium (SABCS)
NCCN 2021 Virtual Annual Conference
NCCN Academy for Excellence & Leadership in Oncology™: School of Pharmaceutical and Biotech Business
Recorded NCCN Academy - June 29, 2020
NCCN Virtual Annual Congress: Hematologic Malignancies™
NCCN Nursing Program: Advancing Oncology Nursing™
NCCN Global Academy for Excellence & Leadership in Oncology™
Treatment of Venous Thromboembolism, December 23
Monthly Oncology Tumor Boards: A Multidisciplinary Approach to Individualized Patient Care
NCCN Virtual Annual Congress: Hematologic Malignancies™
NCCN Virtual Nursing Forum: Advancing Oncology Nursing in Hematologic Malignancies™
NCCN 2020 Virtual Annual Conference
NCCN Oncology Policy Program
Articles
Delivering Value for Patients Across the Oncology Ecosystem
Defining, Measuring, and Applying Quality in an Evolving Health Policy Landscape and the Implications for Cancer Care
The State of Cancer Care in America: Impact of State Policy on Access to High-Quality Cancer Care
Advocating for Equity in Cancer Care
Policy Challenges and Opportunities to Address Changing Paradigms in Cancer Care Delivery
Policy Strategies for the “New Normal” in Health care to Ensure Access to High Quality Cancer Care
NCCN Health Information Technology Licensees
JNCCN — Journal of the National Comprehensive Cancer Network
NCCN Resource Tool: REMS
NCCN Collaboration with the National Business Group on Health
NCCN Virtual Reimbursement Resource Room and Reimbursement App
NCCN Health Information Technology Licensees
NCCN Oncology Research Program (ORP)
Informed Consent Language Database
Points to Consider on the Best Practices for Biorepositories, Registries and Databases
International Adaptations & Translations
NCCN Framework for Resource Stratification of NCCN Guidelines
(NCCN Framework™)
Global Events
NCCN Global Academy for Excellence & Leadership in Oncology™
NCCN Trends™ Global Surveys
Get Involved - Opportunities for Global Collaboration and Sponsorship
Informed Consent Language Database
Points to Consider on the Best Practices for Biorepositories, Registries and Databases
Disclosure Policy for the NCCN Guidelines Panels
Disclosure Policy for the NCCN Oncology Research Program (ORP)
Identifications and Disclosures of Relationships with External Entities
NCCN Privacy Statement
The National Comprehensive Cancer Network®, Inc., (NCCN®) is issuing this privacy statement to keep our valued users informed of activities in place to ensure their privacy. This privacy statement covers the site NCCN.org. If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact Joseph Junod, Director, Information Technology, by
E-mail
or telephone (215.690.0242).
Information Collection and Use
Information Collection
NCCN is the sole owner of the information collected on NCCN.org. NCCN collects information from our users at several different points on this website.
Registration
NCCN occasionally requests information from users of its NCCN Clinical Practice Guidelines in Oncology (NCCN Guidelines®), NCCN Drugs & Biologics Compendium (NCCN Compendium®),
NCCN Chemotherapy Order Templates (NCCN Templates®), NCCN Biomarkers Compendium®, NCCN Guidelines for Patients®, NCCN Trends™ Surveys & Data, and NCCN Continuing Education. NCCN uses this information to contact the user about safety updates and/or services on our site for which they have expressed interest and to advise users about future updates to this site. Based on the user type, visitors will be asked to provide specific, sometimes required, information (such as areas of interest, clinical specialty, or year of graduation), in order for NCCN to provide a more personalized experience on its site.
NCCN Programs, Services and Resources Registration
NCCN requests information from the user on our registration forms. Here a user must provide contact information (such as name and mailing address) as well as financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date if paying by credit card). This information is used for billing purposes for registration fees and/or hotel deposits and/or services or products. If NCCN cannot process an order, this contact information is used to contact the user.
Passwords
Registered users are responsible for taking all reasonable steps to ensure that no unauthorized person shall have access to your NCCN.org passwords or accounts. It is your sole responsibility to (1) control the dissemination and use of activation codes and passwords; (2) authorize, monitor, and control access to and use of your NCCN.org account and password; (3) promptly inform us of any need to deactivate a password. Users grant to NCCN and to all other persons or entities involved in the operation of NCCN.org the right to transmit, monitor, retrieve, store, and use your information in connection with the operation of NCCN.org. NCCN cannot and does not assume any responsibility or liability for any information you submit.
NCCN Continuing Education Registration
NCCN requires visitors to register to use NCCN Continuing Education content. Required information includes first and last name, degree, title, organization, mailing address, username, password and e-mail address. NCCN uses this information to process CME/CE credit, to contact the user about services on this site for which he or she has expressed interest, and to advise users about future updates to this site.
Orders for NCCN Resources
NCCN requires information from users who order NCCN informational resources through our on-line ordering system, Nice Lines Direct Mail. Required information includes first and last name, shipping address, and e-mail address. This information is used to fill requesters' orders. If NCCN or Nice Lines Direct Mail cannot process an order, the information is used to contact the user.
NCCN Online Surveys
From time-to-time, NCCN may provide users the opportunity to participate in surveys on its website. NCCN does not require information from users to complete these periodic online surveys about NCCN programs, services, and resources. For these surveys, it is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as specialty or year of graduation), but encouraged so NCCN can enhance its programs, services and resources. Users have the option to opt-out of these surveys in their user profile.
NCCN often uses a third party service provider to conduct these surveys; that company will be prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share personally identifiable information provided by users through a survey with other third parties unless we give the user prior notice and choice.
Cookies
"Cookies" are small pieces of information stored by a browser on a computer's hard drive. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them, and are unable to do such things as run programs on your computer, plant viruses, or harvest your personal information. The use of cookies is very common on the Internet.
NO personal information is gathered or stored in the cookies placed by the NCCN website. NO personal information is gathered through the use of these cookies. NCCN uses cookies mainly to understand website usage and traffic statistics. NCCN uses Google Analytics to analyze traffic to this website so we can understand our visitors' needs and continually improve this site for them.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. By changing the options on a web browser or using certain software programs, users can control how and whether cookies will be accepted by a browser. Please note that it is possible to block cookie activity from certain websites while permitting cookies from trusted sites.
Information Use
Profile
NCCN stores information that it collects through registration to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that NCCN maintains on individual users which details their viewing preferences and demographics. Consequently, collected information is tied to visitors' personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for users. These profiles may be used to tailor users' visits to our website and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. NCCN does not share your profile with third parties.
Log Files
Like most website servers, NCCN's uses log files. These include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and user activity within this website to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
Communications from the Site
Special Offers and Updates
Registered NCCN visitors will occasionally receive information on new or updated NCCN programs, services, or resources. Opting in means users have asked to be contacted about NCCN programs, services, and resources. Users may opt-out via e-mail or by updating their profile. Users may unsubscribe at any time by contacting us.
Sharing
Legal Disclaimer
Though NCCN makes every effort to preserve user privacy, NCCN may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein NCCN has a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served on our website.
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)
NCCN shares aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. For example, NCCN may describe the number of users by geography or medical specialty. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.
Third Party Intermediaries
NCCN uses an outside fulfillment company to process and ship orders for NCCN products; an e-mail broadcast company to send e-mail announcements about NCCN events and resources; a web hosting company to provide online access to NCCN presentations; an on-line survey vendor to periodically survey groups of NCCN users; and a credit card processing company to bill users for registration. These companies do not retain share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. Registration for NCCN's educational events consists of a link to a site hosted by CVENT; to view this privacy policy statement, go to
https://www.cvent.com/en/privacy-policy.shtml. Registration for NCCN interactive learning consists of links to sites hosted by Clinical Care Options and ReachMD; to view these privacy statements, go to http://www.clinicaloptions.com/Privacy%20Policy.aspx or http://www.reachmd.com/privacy.aspx. Registration to order NCCN resources online consists of a link to a site hosted by Nice Lines Direct Mail; to view this privacy statement, go to
http://pdf.nicelines.com/nccn/web%20privacy%20policy.pdf
.
Registration to access NCCN surveys is hosted on a site by Survey Monkey; to view this privacy statement, go to
http://www.surveymonkey.com/
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that the National Comprehensive Cancer Network, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. NCCN encourages users to be aware when they leave the NCCN site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
Security
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both on-line and off-line.
When NCCN's registration forms ask users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the industry-standard encryption software - Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). While on a secure page, such as a registration form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just "surfing."
NCCN will reveal only the last four digits of your credit card number on confirmation web pages and/or e-mails, but will transmit your entire credit card number to third party companies used to process your orders and to your credit card company.
While NCCN uses SSL encryption to protect sensitive information on-line, NCCN also does everything in its power to protect user information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure, locked environment.
If users have any questions about the security of NCCN.org, please
contact us.
Supplementation of Information
For this website to properly fulfill its obligation to users, it is necessary for NCCN to supplement the information we receive with information from third party sources.
Credit Card Verification and Processing
NCCN uses Authorize.net for credit card processing services to verify a user's address and credit card information for processing.
Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, e-mail or postal address), or if a user no longer desires to receive information, NCCN provides a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can be done by E-mailing our User Support.
Notification of Changes
If NCCN decides to change its privacy policy, NCCN will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places deemed appropriate so our users are always aware of what information NCCN collects, how it is used, and under what circumstances, if any, NCCN discloses it. NCCN will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
If, however, NCCN is going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, NCCN will notify users via e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not NCCN uses their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if NCCN makes any material changes in its privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, NCCN will post a prominent notice on its website notifying users of the change. In some cases where NCCN posts a notice we will also e-mail users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
Contact Information
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please
contact us
.
Quick Links
Clinicians
Patients/Caregivers
Insurers/Employers/Case Managers
Pharma/Biotech
Industry Analysts
COVID-19 Resources
NCCN Guidelines® - FREE
Contact Us
3025 Chemical Road, Suite 100, Plymouth Meeting, PA 19462 • 215.690.0300 • Fax: 215.690.0280Copyright © 2020 National Comprehensive Cancer Network, All Rights Reserved
